[Melody of Golden Age]
[Episode 17]
Just observe and listen.
Don't cause any trouble.
Or you'll be charged with
disrupting the trial.
Your words are quite intimidating.
However, let's not forget,
no matter how low
Ji Fangming's position in the Ministry of Justice is,
he's still an official
appointed by the imperial court.
If you attempt to extract a false confession out of him,
I certainly won't stand by and do nothing.
Ji Fangming.
No matter how many elusive techniques there are,
they are ultimately just tricks.
What's fake is fake.
It's ultimately not the truth.
You've been scheming for so many years,
all because you wanted to know
the truth about what happened at Jinxiu Workshop back then,
right?
What a pity.
You ended up killing the wrong person,
seeking revenge on the wrong target,
and getting used by others without even realizing it.
Save your breath, Miss Yan.
Trying to trick a criminal into confessing,
this tactic
is hardly new.
Since you all want to know,
I'll tell you the truth.
Chen Shoujie and his wife, Mrs. Chen,
were the instigators back then.
Everything that's happened recently
was all done by me alone.
It was all for avenging
the dozen or so people who were wrongfully killed
at Jinxiu Workshop.
Why are you so certain
that what you know
is the whole truth?
Mrs. Chen was originally
an embroiderer at Jinxiu Workshop, too.
To cover for her,
Chen Shoujie took advantage of the case investigation
to erase her background
and arbitrarily alter others' testimonies.
Back then,
before Kong Xianrong sent the summer clothes design
to Princess Runing's mansion for handover,
he personally reviewed it.
It was only after he took it
to verify with the embroiderers that the design was sealed.
Therefore,
it could only have been switched
during the interaction
with the embroiderers.
After the incident,
everyone from Jinxiu Workshop
was detained and interrogated,
except for Mrs. Chen,
who slipped through the net.
After I found out about this,
I went to probe Chen Shoujie.
Shoujie.
Do you remember this?
[Jinxiu Workshop]
Jinxiu Workshop.
No.
It can't be brought up.
Or I can't survive.
I was wrong.
We were wrong.
We don't know anything.
Every grievance has its perpetrator, and every debt has its debtor.
Please don't
come to us for revenge!
Honey!
Don't say anything.
Just because of this,
you were convinced that
Chen Shoujie was the murderer?
Do you know why those people
are so afraid of these illusions?
It's because they know
many people from Jinxiu Workshop died unjustly,
and they fear their vengeful ghosts will come for revenge!
Deep down,
they feel guilty!
There are no ghosts or spirits in this world.
If there are really ghosts in this world,
they only exist in people's hearts.
If you have a clear conscience,
why fear those ghosts
coming to your door?
Lord Shen, you are indeed upright.
But not everyone
is like what you said.
For some people,
even if they've done something wrong,
they'll put on a facade
of being a good person
and blend in with the crowd,
making it difficult for us
to distinguish them from good people.
So,
you killed Mrs. Chen?
That's right!
She deserved to die!
She was the mastermind!
She was the culprit
who switched the summer clothes
design.
Jinxiu Workshop.
I knew you'd come.
Do you have any last words?
It's time to pay the price.
I killed her
only to console
my brother's spirit in heaven.
What's wrong with that?
Even for those who have committed unforgivable crimes,
it's up to the imperial law to punish them.
If you have grievances, you can seek justice
and appeal the case.
But taking the law into your own hands and committing murder
is simply wrong.
That's easy for you to say.
Seek justice?
Appeal the case?
So many years have passed.
Who doesn't know that the Jinxiu Workshop case was a miscarriage of justice?
But who
has been willing to stand up and speak the truth?
Not to mention others.
Just take you as an example.
You hold a high position,
and you're deeply trusted by the Grand Empress Dowager,
yet you've allowed this case
to be buried for so many years
without ever speaking up.
Since that's the case,
I might as well
deal with them myself.
So after you killed Mrs. Chen,
you deliberately left
the traumatized and mentally unstable Chen Shoujie alive.
It wasn't out of consideration for old times' sake,
but because you wanted to torment him while he's still alive,
right?
That's correct.
Mrs. Chen was the main culprit.
Surely she deserved to die.
As for Chen Shoujie,
I didn't kill him
not because I didn't want to.
He sheltered the murderer,
so he couldn't escape blame.
Killing him
would have been too easy on him.
It suddenly occurred to me,
why not use another method
to torture him to death?
So that he could truly experience
what it's like to be in a wrongful case,
losing family and close friends,
and experience the feeling of helplessness
and despair!
Xianrong.
I've finally
brought justice for you all.
[Moths to a flame. Born at dawn, dead by dusk. Not entering the cycle of reincarnation. Immortal reincarnation.]
Those people
deserve to never
be reincarnated!
But now,
he has gone mad,
and yet you
still choose to believe
that he is innocent!
You just refuse to accept the fact
that the Jinxiu Workshop case was a miscarriage of justice!
Therefore,
you are also guilty!
You
should all pay the price for this!
What Huo'e?
Huo'e! Huo'e! Huo'e!
[Mingsheng Temple]
This was
found at Chen Shoujie's mansion.
It's fabric from Jinxiu Workshop.
If they really were
the instigators as you said,
then why would they
carefully preserve
something that constantly reminds them
of their crimes?
This is impossible.
Perhaps you're not the only one
who feels helpless and bitter
about what happened back then.
I can't be wrong.
I absolutely cannot be wrong.
Maybe you've just been so focused on revenge
that you failed to notice
that what Mrs. Chen had been staring at until she died
was the hidden compartment in the beam
where the fabric was hidden.
Perhaps she wanted to say something,
but she never got the chance.
It was all my fault.
I shouldn't have kept the truth
hidden for so many years.
I was afraid of dying.
To protect my family,
I ended up harming so many people.
I deserve to die.
In the end, there is no concealing the truth.
The truth is about to be revealed
to the world.
Kong.
I've let you down.
It was because of my cowardice
that I got coerced
into hastily closing the case.
I never thought...
I never thought that...
You were coerced?
Who exactly coerced you?
Tell me!
What's the use of admitting your mistake now?
So many people were wrongly accused and died.
So many wronged souls
are unable to rest in peace.
As a government official,
you feared the real culprit
and covered up the truth.
Even if you admit your mistake now,
can those people
be brought back to life?
Who exactly coerced you?
Huo'e! Huo'e! Huo'e!
Chen Huo'e! Chen Huo'e! Chen Huo'e!
Chen Huo'e! Chen Huo'e!
It's Chen Huo'e again.
No way.
I couldn't have killed the wrong person.
Mrs. Chen was definitely the murderer.
She wouldn't have lied to me.
So who instructed you
to lead Yan Xing to Mingsheng Temple?
So I was really being used?
I was really being used?
Everyone laughs
at the moths flying into the flame,
but little do they know that
mayflies live and die in a day,
not entering the cycle of reincarnation.
The moths endure the fire and do not die,
being reincarnated in the cycle!
Ji Fangming, wake up!
Kong Xianrong proclaimed his innocence until his dying breath.
All he wanted was to clear his name
and uncover the truth.
However, you were blinded by hatred
and used by others to kill the innocent.
How is this any different
from those who
harmed Jinxiu Workshop back then?
Now the evidence is conclusive,
and you still dare to spread rumors here!
Grand Commander Shen.
Don't you want to know
how Chen Huo'e came back from the dead
and tell me the other culprits involved
in the Jinxiu Workshop case?
The real culprit is...
Princess Ying!
It's Princess Ying.
She's jealous of talent
and has long harbored dissatisfied with Princess Runing.
So she used Jinxiu Workshop
to frame her for treason.
Shut your mouth!
It's not just Princess Ying!
Prince Xian is also involved!
He's also unwilling to remain inferior to Princess Ying.
To seize power and authority,
he eliminated his opponents!
And there's also...
The Grand Empress Dowager!
They are all murderers!
You, all of you!
Every one of you is a murderer!
You're falsely accusing the royal family
and slandering the Grand Empress Dowager
just to cause a commotion
and get us to reopen the Jinxiu Workshop case.
Grand Commander Shen.
This is a serious matter. A serious matter indeed.
Reopening old cases would implicate many.
Please don't bring trouble upon yourself.
As for the ravings of this madman,
let's pretend we didn't hear them.
We didn't hear them.
Wu Taiming,
you corrupt official!
I, Ji Fangming, am not crazy.
I, Ji Fangming,
am very clear-headed now.
Every word comes from the bottom of my heart.
I wonder if Grand Commander Shen
dares to report what I've said,
word for word,
to the Grand Empress Dowager?
You just can't wait
to die, can you?
If my life
can appease the spirits of those
who have passed,
it'll be worth it.
If that's the case,
I'll grant your wish.
I will report what happened today
truthfully to
the Grand Empress Dowager.
Lord Lai.
What do you think?
Grand Commander Shen, you're the presiding judge here.
On behalf of the Imperial Investigation Department,
I'm merely here to observe
the murder case of Mrs. Chen.
As for how the Imperial Security Bureau decides,
it's up to you, Grand Commander.
One is indifferent,
and the other is cunning and sly.
They both try to keep their hands clean.
I, Ji Fangming,
on behalf of the wrongfully killed people from Jinxiu Workshop,
thank you, Lord Shen.
I've certainly gained some insight
into your intelligence and courage
today, Miss Yan.
I wonder if you'd be interested
in coming to work with me at the Imperial Investigation Department.
I'm in need of
capable people like you.
Lord Wu.
I believe you wouldn't be so petty
as to hold onto talent so tightly, right?
Lord Lai, you must be joking.
Although Yan Xing
is part of the Ministry of Justice,
she is, more importantly,
the wife of the Grand Commander of the Imperial Security Bureau.
Lord Lai.
You don't plan to
take my person away right in front of me, do you?
Grand Commander, given what you said,
it seems I'm
hasty and inconsiderate.
I simply wanted
to recruit some talent under my wing.
Grand Commander, you're overthinking it.
Overthinking?
After all these years,
Lord Lai,
your ability to turn the tables
hasn't changed one bit.
In matters of officialdom,
family affairs shouldn't get involved in the first place.
Given your way of doing things, Grand Commander Shen,
I'm afraid Miss Yan
won't have an easy time of it,
spending all day solving cases with you.
Moreover,
a good bird chooses the tree upon which to perch.
In terms of talent selection,
with such a promising future ahead,
Grand Commander, you shouldn't stand in her way.
I'm quite content,
perching on this tree.
You know,
I'm lazy and love to eat.
I don't really want to change jobs at the moment.
Thank you for your kind offer,
Lord Lai.
If that's the case,
let's wait and see
how good this tree you've chosen
can be.
They say,
"Husband and wife are like birds of the same forest,
but they fly apart when disaster strikes."
Lord Wu.
What's your opinion on that?
Well,
I'm not very clever.
When it comes to matters of love,
I can't figure them out.
I really can't.
"Matters of love", you say.
Interesting.
"This is a serious matter. A serious matter indeed.
Reopening old cases would implicate many.
Please don't bring trouble upon yourself."
"As for how the Imperial Security Bureau decides,
it's up to you, Grand Commander."
What are you thinking about?
You seem lost in thought.
I'm so tired.
I need to go and get some rest.
Is something wrong?
It seems Yun Que
is particularly concerned about this interrogation.
The old case of Jinxiu Workshop.
She came here for this in the first place.
Now,
she finally can't hold back anymore.
So,
you deliberately kept her in the mansion
just to find out
whether her appearance was a coincidence,
or if someone was behind it,
pushing things along?
Jing Lin has investigated her.
She doesn't know much
about this matter indeed.
However...
However what?
However, her parents
had quite a lot of business dealings
with Jinxiu Workshop back then,
but they weren't implicated.
If it was for self-preservation
that they hid the evidence,
then why,
after Chen Huo'e appeared,
did they steal the evidence and come to seek justice?
Don't you think it was too much of a coincidence?
If that's the case,
why don't you
ask them to clarify?
The time isn't right,
and trying to keep them alive to testify
might not be an easy task either.
We're out in the open,
while others are in the shadows.
Please let me
handle this.
It's just that
the old case of Jinxiu Workshop involves many people.
Even Wu Taiming and Lai Luozhi
are eager to distance themselves from it.
It seems the truth of the matter
is far beyond my expectations,
and things might get even deeper.
I didn't expect
that the fearless Yan Xing
would also have moments of fear.
Are you really
going to report
Ji Fangming's unorthodox words
as well?
For the Jinxiu Workshop case,
I promised someone
to investigate it personally.
Someone?
Could it be Princess Runing?
The ignorant are fearless,
while those who know are deeply afraid.
I finally understand
the difference between you and me.
You've long anticipated this day,
yet you remain so calm.
All of this doesn't sound like
what you usually say.
If it were you normally,
upon hearing about a wrongful case,
you would have jumped up to investigate immediately.
No one could have stopped you.
Of course.
We must right every wrong
and speak out against injustice.
That's what it means to be a good government official,
worthy of the court's salary.
But
I know
what it means to
reopen the Jinxiu Workshop case.
Just based on Ji Fangming's few words,
I'm afraid...
You've improved.
That wrongful conviction from back then
caused quite a sensation,
leaving many people
with lingering fears.
Reopening the old case now
will inevitably bring back
those old shadows.
When that happens,
no one will be able to avoid it.
That's right.
They intend to use Ji Fangming
to bring people's attention to
the old case of Jinxiu Workshop,
so as to make people suspicious of the royal family
and cause unrest.
In the end, Ji Fangming
must have realized
that he was being used,
but he had no choice.
It's pitiful.
And tragic.
[Peace and Prosperity]
How confident are you
about the Jinxiu Workshop case?
That's why I'm worried.
This case is years old.
If you bring it up to the Grand Empress Dowager abruptly,
first, the Grand Empress Dowager
might disagree with reopening the case.
And second, what if she takes her anger out on you?
What should we...
[Peace and Prosperity]
So after leaving the Ministry of Justice,
you've been worried all the way
about me?
I'm not worried about you at all.
I'm just worried you may get me involved.
[Peace and Prosperity]
After all,
I now have
the identity of Mrs. Shen
to uphold.
Besides, there are all these people
in this household
that I have to consider, right?
Everyone's position is difficult.
The wronged want to reopen old cases,
while what the Grand Empress Dowager wants
is just peace in the realm
and happiness for the people.
So what are you going to do?
Don't worry about me.
As for this matter,
your husband is here to handle it.
I've already said I'm not worried about you.
Then, I'll leave this matter at home
to you, Honey.
Since you know she's trouble,
why do you still keep her in the mansion?
She might
still have important evidence on her.
Is this your explanation?
You're truly cold and heartless, White Ghost,
always causing trouble for others.
Well,
Jing Lin.
Continue to keep an eye on Yun Que.
If there's a chance,
see if
she's still hiding anything
on the Jinxiu Workshop case.
Got it.
[Guangyue Restaurant]
Kidnap someone for me.
I don't mean for you to actually kidnap them.
I just need you, Pan,
to go to Jiangnan in person
and bring that person safely to Xiang'an.
Jiangnan?
I remember that Yun Que in the Shen household,
who competed with you for the position of legitimate wife,
is also from Jiangnan, isn't she?
Could it be you're jealous of her,
so you want to...
Please.
Great talent Pan.
Pan. Pan Chi.
You're the only one who can help me with this.
I beg you, please.
It's not really a big deal.
It's just
a bit of legwork, though.
Don't you worry about that.
When you come back,
I'll definitely treat you to a grand feast
and some top-quality wine.
Besides, I can tell
you're not just an ordinary merchant.
I definitely won't expose you
and cause trouble.
Are you threatening me?
Of course not.
How could I?
After all, we're
friends who help each other.
Just friends, huh?
What's that?
Nothing.
I'll be waiting for your treat then.
Oh, by the way.
Take this
with you.
It's right on your way.
What's this?
This is the list of victims
Chen Huo'e killed back then.
You...
For these crossed-out names,
their crime scenes are all near Xiang'an City
[Lyu Ruozhi, Zhao Caiwei, Song Zhilan]
or not far away.
You'll pass by a few of them on your trip.
Just investigate a bit
about the victims' situations.
Trying to get a free meal from you
is really not easy.
Oh, right.
This thingy.
You take it.
I just acquired it.
Why are you giving me a fan?
Is there some trick to it?
Be careful with it.
It has a mechanism.
The handle is hollow.
You can put powder inside.
With just a light flick,
you can secretly
scatter the powder.
The handle is hollow.
So this is for poisoning?
Well, not exactly.
The so-called secret weapons
depend on who uses them
and how they're used.
You're giving me such a rare item.
You're not...
You're not planning to force me to buy it, are you?
Well, you keep it for now.
If you find it useful,
you can pay me later.
Isn't that still forcing me to buy it?
Is there poison inside?
It won't kill a person,
but it can easily
knock out a bull.
Have you all heard?
The ruins of Jinxiu Workshop
have shown another miracle.
Really?
Swarms of moths flocked to the wall,
and the blood from the moths' corpses formed words.
Even flying insects are
crying out for justice for the old case of Jinxiu Workshop.
The reborn Huo'e...
How bizarre.
Is about to seek revenge on the real culprit!
The Jinxiu Workshop incident
happened so many years ago.
Why is something like this suddenly happening now?
Haven't you heard?
More people have been beheaded
because of the Jinxiu Workshop incident.
This has caused unrest among the people.
This case must have been a miscarriage of justice.
Too many people died tragically back then
and they couldn't get justice.
That must be why they linger in this world.
These wronged souls,
they won't just randomly seek revenge on anyone, will they?
We're all innocent, you know.
I heard
only by reopening this case
and bringing justice to the deceased
can these wronged souls
rest in peace.
[Cautiousness and Leniency]
Why aren't you eating?
If you don't eat soon, the noodles will get soggy.
You came back so late.
You must have eaten out, haven't you?
Of course.
No matter how tired or exhausted I am,
I can't let myself starve.
These past few days,
I've done so many things.
It's worn me out.
Come on, eat.
You know what?
I went to investigate Jinxiu Workshop at night.
As expected, I saw what looked like ghost fires
floating in the air.
There was always something floating around,
but I couldn't see it clearly.
This must be
the ghost shadows that the common people
have been talking about.
On my way back,
I saw
that every household on the street
next to Jinxiu Workshop
had hung this
Fire Moth Jade at their doorway.
Investigating alone at night,
don't you find it creepy?
Those are all fake.
I suppose
it must be the resurrected
Chen Huo'e's doing.
But as for ghost fires,
I see them quite often
in graveyards during summer.
My master once told me
that it's because when corpses decompose,
they produce some kind of
imperceptible substance,
which gets ignited
in the dry air.
The method for ghost shadows
should be similar, I guess.
It's just the shadow of
a fast-moving black bird or beast.
As expected,
you know everything.
Are you doing this on purpose?
The area where Jinxiu Workshop is located
should have been
guarded by the Imperial Security Bureau.
But this afternoon,
when the moths swarmed on the wall,
causing the so-called miracle,
the guards didn't disperse the crowd.
Jing Lin was clearly around,
but he just watched from afar.
So?
The Imperial Security Bureau has many things to investigate.
Ji Fangming has already been arrested.
There's no need to bother with those things.
Aren't you waiting?
Waiting for what?
Waiting for a gust
that could help reopen
the Jinxiu Workshop case.
You went out for a bit
and brought something back, huh?
Be careful.
Don't mess with it.
Don't mess with it...
Why so nervous?
Who gave it to you?
I haven't paid
for this fan yet.
Don't break it.
Is that so?
What's with you lately?
You've been acting so strange.
Have I?
Yes, you have.
In the future, if I
don't have time to make the medicated diet,
you must eat on time
and not starve yourself.
Also,
don't suddenly say
some nonsensical things,
and then put on
some frightening pose.
Also, don't suddenly...
Suddenly what?
Just suddenly...
Don't waste food.
Alright.
If you don't allow it, I'll listen to you.
But from now on,
don't do such dangerous things
like investigating Jinxiu Workshop at night
again.
Fortunately, there were people I arranged
guarding there tonight.
Otherwise...
You really don't take your life seriously.
I'll only allow this once.
Don't let it happen again.
What's happening?
My head is so dizzy.
No way.
Pan Chi.
You've really got me in trouble this time.
Yan Xing?
Knock Out A Bull...
This...
♫The night is still young, and the moonlight reflects on the west window♫
♫There are stars in your eyes♫
It smells so good.
♫When I touch you♫
♫My heart is like a flickering candlelight, shaking and swaying♫
♫The more I care, the deeper I hide♫
♫Leaves turn yellow and fall, and my thoughts run in thousands of lines♫
You're taking all the advantages.
♫Time is like a poem, romantic and sorrowful♫
♫Two hearts♫
♫Collide between dawn and dusk♫
♫The embrace came as a surprise♫
♫I want to be with you, side by side♫
♫I want to keep you by my side♫
♫Through the obstacle of wind and rain♫
♫I want to be your moonlight♫
♫Accompany you until every dawn♫
♫How I wish♫
♫I could just forget the passage of time like this♫
♫I want to be with you, side by side♫
♫May we never forget each other♫
♫There will always be a place for us to meet♫
♫I want to be with you forever♫
♫When our black hair turns grey♫
♫In this life♫
♫I'll only cherish you in my heart♫
No.
Don't.
♫I want to be with you, side by side♫
♫I want to keep you by my side♫
♫Through the obstacle of wind and rain♫
♫I want to be your moonlight♫
♫Accompany you until every dawn♫
♫How I wish♫
♫I could just forget the passage of time like this♫
♫I want to be with you, side by side♫
♫I want to keep you by my side♫
♫Through the obstacle of wind and rain♫
♫I want to be your moonlight♫
♫Accompany you until every dawn♫
♫How I wish♫
♫I could just forget the passage of time like this♫
♫I want to be with you, side by side♫
It seems we really need to
♫May we never forget each other♫
♫There will always be a place for us to meet♫
pay for this fan.
♫I want to be with you forever♫
♫When our black hair turns grey♫
♫In this life♫
♫I'll only cherish you in my heart♫
Let Madam sleep as much as she wants.
No need to wake her up.
Understood.
What a character, this Ji Fangming.
Showing no courtesy of being an official
is already a great disrespect.
He even dared
to use the old case of Jinxiu Workshop
to slander and frame Prince Xian and Princess Ying.
He truly deserves to die a thousand deaths.
Your Majesty.
Ji Fangming has committed numerous evil deeds.
His death would be no loss.
However, behind this case,
there's someone else instigating
and using Ji Fangming's obsession
to spread terror.
Who is that?
It is none other than
the serial killer who was arrested
and committed suicide five years ago,
Chen Huo'e.
What?
A dead person
could still cause such a stir
in Xiang'an City?
I remember
that this case
was personally investigated by you back then, Lai Luozhi.
What exactly is this about?
Your Majesty.
The case of Chen Huo'e back then
caused widespread panic.
Therefore,
after I captured Chen Huo'e,
I executed her publicly.
At that time,
half of Xiang'an City's residents
witnessed Chen Huo'e
commit suicide in public.
In front of everyone,
her corpse was thrown into the mass grave.
It's just...
It's just what?
It's just Chen Huo'e publicly declared
the mad words that she would come back to life.
So you mean,
she has really come back to life?
Recently,
there have indeed been rumors
of Chen Huo'e's appearance.
There's even a group of followers
who believe that person is the same Chen Huo'e
who was arrested and committed suicide five years ago.
However, I believe
it's just someone with ulterior motives
causing trouble
and misleading people.
My dear ministers.
Chen Huo'e's fabrication of miracles
has caused the people to suspect
that there was injustice concerning the old Jinxiu Workshop case.
The Imperial Security Bureau has reported
and applied for the reinvestigation
of the two old cases of
Chen Huo'e and Jinxiu Workshop as one.
What are your opinions on this?
You love the people like your own children, Your Majesty.
Now that Grand Commander Shen
intends to reopen this case,
I find it quite appropriate.
Mr. Lai.
Do you have any special insights?
In my humble opinion,
the sudden resurfacing of the old case of Jinxiu Workshop
may have hidden implications.
However,
whether this old case will disturb
the peace of Xiang'an City,
I dare not speculate.
Your Majesty.
I have just retrieved the previous case files,
and upon careful examination, I discovered
there are still some unresolved questions.
You've always been attentive to the people's concerns
and compassionate towards their lives, Your Majesty.
I understand this matter is troublesome,
but I dare not withhold the truth in my report.
Your Majesty.
I believe
Commander Shen's words are quite reasonable.
If we can investigate this matter thoroughly,
it will bring peace and comfort to the people,
which is surely what you desire, Mother.
This action will also
demonstrate your heart for relieving the people's hardships and concerns
to all the people.
What a fine idea, relieving the people's concerns.
Mr. Shen.
I hereby entrust this case
entirely to you.
You must investigate it thoroughly.
I accept the command.
I won't disappoint your expectations, Your Majesty.
I will apprehend the culprit as soon as possible.
What's your opinion on Grand Commander Shen's decision
to reopen this case?
The incident from back then
caused widespread panic.
I take my leave, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
You've never interfered much with state affairs.
This time, it seems
you've drawn attention to yourself.
Mentor.
I didn't think too much this time.
I just wanted to see how Shen Du
would handle this investigation.
Back then, when Princess Runing
was implicated in the Jinxiu Workshop case,
there were suspicions
that it was the doing of Princess Ying,
who was at odds with Princess Runing.
If the reopening of this case
can reveal the truth
and implicate Princess Ying,
it would be
great news for us.
We could use their hands
to eliminate your rivals, Your Highness.
Mentor, you're overthinking it.
I simply want to uncover
the truth of what happened back then, that's all.